Contact

elishaadewuyi@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/adewuyielisha-opeoluwa-a3a2ba211 (LinkedIn)

twitter.com/MhiztaLOEL (Other)

Top Skills

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) Social Media Social Media Marketing

Certifications

DeFi - How to invest in the best

Adewuyi Elisha Opeoluwa

Community Manager | Crypto trader | Social media manager | Frontend Developer | Director @invigorateDAO

Ibadan, Oyo, Nigeria

Summary

Experienced community manager with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Fisheries, Online Community Moderation, Social Media, Graphics, and Crypto.

Strong community and social services professional with a Barchelor of fisheries focused in Marine Biology and Biological Oceanography from University of Port Harcourt.

Experience

Arc76 space Community Manager June 2022 - Present (4 months) Near ecosystem

The first season with Arc76 is about exploring space and expansion into the unknown. A time for people and communities alike to learn about the systems provided to them and to set up a home while getting to know their neighbors.

INVIGORATE DAO

Managing Director February 2022 - Present (8 months)

Crypto Bank Community Manager January 2022 - Present (9 months) **United States**

CryptoPhd

Community Manager November 2021 - Present (11 months)

Project management and blockchain marketing services

Bluzelle

Ambassador May 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Content creation

Meme creation

Info graphic designing

Social media promotion

500seasons

Social Media Manager

March 2022 - July 2022 (5 months)

- Content creation
- Boosting twitter engagement
- Publication of contents

Friendlyseacreatures

Communty moderator

February 2022 - July 2022 (6 months)

- Organizations of local events and games
- Customer support
- Social media marketing planning

Metarising by MicroTuber

Community moderator

February 2022 - July 2022 (6 months)

South Korea

- Moderating the discord channel
- Customer support
- Organisation of local events

DoomHero Game

Community Manager

December 2021 - February 2022 (3 months)

Remote

Recruiting local community moderators

Contributing to the growth of the community

GameFi protocol

Global Ambassador

September 2021 - January 2022 (5 months)

Content creation

Article writing

Graphic designing

Meme creation

ABCC Exchange
Listing Ambassador
August 2021 - November 2021 (4 months)
Singapore, Singapore

LBank

4 months

community manager ambassador July 2021 - October 2021 (4 months) Manage a Nigeria sub telegram group Doing research about crypto market

promoter/campus partner
July 2021 - September 2021 (3 months)

Education

University of Port Harcourt

Barchelor of fisheries, Marine Biology and Biological

Oceanography · (2018 - 2023)